Usage: next build [directory] [options]

Creates an optimized production build of your application. The output displays
information about each route.

Arguments:
  [directory]                              A directory on which to build the application. If no directory is provided, the current directory will be used.

Options:
  -d, --debug                              Enables a more verbose build output.
  --no-lint                                Disables linting.
  --no-mangling                            Disables mangling.
  --profile                                Enables production profiling for React.
  --experimental-app-only                  Builds only App Router routes.
  --experimental-build-mode [mode]         Uses an experimental build mode. (choices: "compile", "generate", default: "default")
  --experimental-debug-memory-usage        Enables memory profiling features to debug memory consumption.
  --experimental-upload-trace, <traceUrl>  Reports a subset of the debugging trace to a remote HTTP URL. Includes sensitive data.
  -h, --help                               Displays this message.
